http://www.churchofgladtidings.org/privacy-policy/

About Us
Our New ChurchPlan Your VisitWhat To ExpectWhat We BelieveLeadership
G T
HomeAbout UsOur New ChurchPlan Your VisitWhat To ExpectWhat We BelieveLeadershipOur MinistriesRoyal RangersMpact Girls MinistryRock Solid KidzSermonsEventsContact UsGT Facebook
login
Privacy PolicyServices
Sunday school - 9:30AM
&
10:30AM worship / Wednesday: 6:30PM Adult, Youth and Kids Ministries
cancel
saveIntroductionThe Church of Glad Tidings ("we” or “us”) values its visitors’ privacy. This privacy policy is effective March 14, 2020; it summarizes what information we might collect from a registered user or other visitor (“you”), and what we will and will not do with it.Please note that this privacy policy does not govern the collection and use of information by companies that The Church of Glad Tidings does not control, nor by individuals not employed or managed by The Church of Glad Tidings. If you visit a Web site that we mention or link to, be sure to review its privacy policy before providing the site with information.What we do with your personally identifiable informationIt is always up to you whether to disclose personally identifiable information to us, although if you elect not to do so, we reserve the right not to register you as a user or provide you with any products or services. “Personally identifiable information” means information that can be used to identify you as an individual, such as, for example:your name, email address, phone number, billing address, and shipping addressyour name, user ID and passwordcredit card informationThe above provision may not be appropriate if credit card information is handled by a payment processor.any account-preference information you provide usyour computer’s domain name and IP address, indicating where your computer is located on the Internetsession data for your login session, so that our computer can ‘talk’ to yours while you are logged inIf you do provide personally identifiable information to us, either directly or through a reseller or other partner, we will:not sell or rent it to a third party without your permission — although unless you opt out (see below), we may use your contact information to provide you with information we believe you need to know or may find useful, such as (for example) news about our church, services and modifications to the Terms of Service;take commercially reasonable precautions to protect the information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction;not use or disclose the information except:as necessary to provide services or products you have ordered, such as (for example) by providing it to a carrier to deliver products you have ordered;in other ways described in this privacy policy or to which you have otherwise consented;in the aggregate with other information in such a way so that your identity cannot reasonably be determined (for example, statistical compilations);as required by law, for example, in response to a subpoena or search warrant;to outside auditors who have agreed to keep the information confidential;as necessary to enforce the Terms of Service;as necessary to protect the rights, safety, or property of The Church of Glad Tidings, its users, or others; this may include (for example) exchanging information with other organizations for fraud protection and/or risk reduction.Other information we collectWe may collect other information that cannot be readily used to identify you, such as (for example) the domain name and IP address of your computer. We may use this information, individually or in the aggregate, for technical administration of our Web site(s); research and development; account administration; and to help us focus our marketing efforts more precisely.CookiesThe Church of Glad Tidings uses “cookies” to store personal data on your computer. We may also link information stored on your computer in cookies with personal data about specific individuals stored on our servers. If you set up your Web browser (for example, Internet Explorer or Firefox) so that cookies are not allowed, you might not be able to use some or all of the features of our Web site(s).External data storage sitesWe may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.Your privacy responsibilitiesTo help protect your privacy, be sure:not to share your user ID or password with anyone else;to log off the The Church of Glad Tidings Web site when you are finished;to take customary precautions to guard against “malware” (viruses, Trojan horses, bots, etc.), for example by installing and updating suitable anti-virus software.Notice to European Union usersThe Church of Glad Tidings is located in the United States. If you provide information to us, the information will be transferred out of the European Union (EU) to the United States. By providing personal information to us, you are consenting to its storage and use as described herein.Information collected from childrenYou must be at least 13 years old to use The Church of Glad Tidings‘s Web site(s). The Church of Glad Tidings does not knowingly collect information from children under 13. (See the U.S. Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.)Changes to this privacy policyWe reserve the right to change this privacy policy as we deem necessary or appropriate because of legal compliance requirements or changes in our business practices. If you have provided us with an email address, we will endeavor to notify you, by email to that address, of any material change to how we will use personally identifiable information.Questions or comments?If you have questions or comments about The Church of Glad Tidings's privacy policy, contact us via any of the ways described in the Contact page at cs3139491.churchspring.org.
Register for this event
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
Comments
Thanks for registering!Your registration has been received.
×
Email a Friend
URL: https://www.churchofgladtidings.org/privacy-policy/
Send
Thanks for sharing!Your email has been sent.
×LoginInvalid login info
Login
forgot password?or
Login with Facebook
Login with Twitter
Don't have an account? Request one!
Enter your email below and a new password will be sent to you.
After you login with this new password you can change it in the settings area.
Email
Cancel
Reset PasswordYour New Password Has Been Sent!
We have just sent an email containing a new password to login.
You can always change this password by logging in and visiting the settings page.
OK
×Request an Account
First Name
Last Name
Email
Password
×Create an Account
Your request for an account has been received.
Once this information is moderated you will receive an email with your account details.
OKWelcome to your new website!We are excited you've joined the ChurchSpring family! It is our desire to come along side your ministry as you seek to reach the world for Christ.
We would like to take you through a quick tutorial to get you on your way. Click continue to get started.
ContinueMaximum Navigation Items ReachedYou have reached the limit of 6 main level navigation items.
You can always rename or delete your existing main nav items to better organize your content.
Consider adding pages to the sub navigation menus as well.
OkAre you sure you want to delete this item?
Notification Text
DismissNotification Textcontent
DismissSavingWe are processing your request. Please do not click anything until this process is completed. Thank you.
